https://www.newdinosaurs.com/privacy-policy/

HomeList of DinosaursFacts & FAQPrehistoric AnimalsPrehistoric Birds, Fish, Amphibians…Prehistoric AmphibiansPrehistoric BirdsPrehistoric FishPrehistoric SharksPrehistoric TetrapodsPrehistoric MammalsMarsupial EvolutionMegafauna MammalsPrehistoric DogsPrehistoric ElephantsPrehistoric HorsesPrehistoric PrimatesPrehistoric WhalesSaber-Toothed CatsThe First MammalsPrehistoric ReptilesBefore The DinosaursPlesiosaurs and PliosaursPrehistoric CrocodilesPrehistoric SnakesPrehistoric TurtlesThe “Fish Lizards”The First ReptilesThe Flying ReptilesThe Marine Reptiles of The Late CretaceousPaleoartists
Search HomeList of DinosaursFacts & FAQPrehistoric AnimalsPrehistoric Birds, Fish, Amphibians…Prehistoric AmphibiansPrehistoric BirdsPrehistoric FishPrehistoric SharksPrehistoric TetrapodsPrehistoric MammalsMarsupial EvolutionMegafauna MammalsPrehistoric DogsPrehistoric ElephantsPrehistoric HorsesPrehistoric PrimatesPrehistoric WhalesSaber-Toothed CatsThe First MammalsPrehistoric ReptilesBefore The DinosaursPlesiosaurs and PliosaursPrehistoric CrocodilesPrehistoric SnakesPrehistoric TurtlesThe “Fish Lizards”The First ReptilesThe Flying ReptilesThe Marine Reptiles of The Late CretaceousPaleoartists
Privacy policyLast Edited: January 28, 2019About our Privacy PolicyThis privacy policy explains how our site (“New Dinosaurs”), will use the personal information that is collected when you use the website at https://www.newdinosaurs.com and/or other New Dinosaurs services that post a link to this privacy policy (“Service”). This policy may be supplemented by additional privacy terms or notices set forth on certain areas of New Dinosaurs.1. Information We CollectNew Dinosaurs collects information from you in two ways: directly from your input and automatically from your use.a. Information You ProvideThe types of personal information that New Dinosaurs collects directly from you may include:Contact details, such as your name, email address, postal address and telephone number;Usernames and passwords;Job details and other professional background information;Comments, feedback and other information that you submit to New Dinosaurs; andInterests and communications preferences.b. Information Collected AutomaticallyNew Dinosaurs also automatically collects certain information that tells us how you use New Dinosaurs services, including:Internet Protocol (“IP”) address used to connect your computer to the Internet;Computer, device and connection information, such as browser type and version, operating system, mobile platform, unique device identifier (“UDID”) and other technical identifiers;Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) click stream data, including date and time stamp, referring and exit URLs, search terms you used and pages you visited or searched for on New Dinosaurs; andFor location-aware services, the physical location of your device in order to provide you with more relevant content for where you are in the world.We may use and disclose information that does not reveal your identity or permit direct association with any specific individual, such as browser and device information, anonymous usage data and aggregated information, for any purpose, except where we are restricted by law. When we combine non-personal information with personal information, the combined information will be treated as personal information for as long as it remains combined.c. Cookies and Similar TechnologiesCookies are small text files containing a string of characters sent to your computer or another device that you are using to access New Dinosaurs services. We use cookies and similar technologies to collect and store your preferences and other information about your use of New Dinosaurs services.You can manage cookies through your browser’s settings and other tools. However, if you refuse certain cookies, some features of New Dinosaurs services may not function properly. To find out more about how we use cookies, read our Cookies Policy.2. Disclosure of Your Personal InformationWe use your personal information to:Provide New Dinosaurs services to you;Respond to your requests, inquiries, comments or concerns;Enable you to personalize New Dinosaurs services and to select content you want to access or to share with a third party;Notify you about changes or updates to New Dinosaurs and other products and services, including those belonging to related third parties;Provide you special offers and other information about related events, products and services and to invite you to participate in surveys, competitions, and promotions, as determined by your choices and communications preferences;Evaluate and improve New Dinosaurs and other products and services and to develop new products or services;Identify and analyze usage trends and determine the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns;Provide technical, product and other support and help keep New Dinosaurs services working, safe and secure; andComply with our legal obligations.We may also combine the personal information that you provide with information that we obtain from other sources or that already exists in our records for the purposes described above. Any use of your personal information for a purpose other than those described in this privacy policy will require your express consent.3. Disclosure of Your Personal InformationWe share your personal information with:Our service providers, suppliers, agents, and representatives, including customer support, email and IT service providers to process the information for us based on our instructions and in compliance with this privacy policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.We also may share your personal information with our affiliates and non-affiliated third parties that wish to send you information about related products and services that may be of interest to you.We also may need to disclose your personal information:to respond to or comply with any law, regulation, subpoena, court order or other legal obligation;to enforce and protect our rights and properties;to detect, investigate and help prevent security threats, fraud or other malicious activity;to protect the rights, property or safety of our users, employees or others; andif New Dinosaurs or a related asset or line of business is acquired by, transferred to or merged with another company.New Dinosaurs may let you post and share personal information, comments, materials and other content. Any information that you disclose publicly may be collected and used by others, may be indexable by search engines, and might not be able to be removed. Please be careful when disclosing personal information in these public areas.4. Children’s PrivacyNew Dinosaurs do not knowingly collect information from children under the age of 13 and New Dinosaurs’s products and services are not targeted at children under 13.5. Your Communications PreferencesYou can manage your communications preferences when you register for New Dinosaurs services, by updating your account preferences, by using the “opt-out” or unsubscribe mechanism or other means provided within the communications that you receive, or by contacting us. We reserve the right to notify you of changes or updates to New Dinosaurs services whenever necessary.6. Access to Your Personal InformationNew Dinosaurs may allow registered users to directly access their account information and make corrections or updates upon login at any time. The accuracy of such information is solely the responsibility of the user.You may also request access to other personal information about you that you have provided to us through New Dinosaurs and have any inaccuracies corrected by contacting us, subject to applicable law. To protect your privacy and security, we may require you to verify your identity.If you request to deactivate your account or delete your personal information, we will endeavor to fulfill your request in accordance with our policies but some personal information may persist in backup copies for a certain period of time and may be retained as necessary for legitimate business purposes or to comply with our legal obligations.7. Data SecurityWe use a variety of administrative, physical and technical security measures intended to safeguard your personal information.8. Changes to Privacy PolicyWe may change this privacy policy from time to time. Any changes will be posted on this page with an updated revision date. Unless otherwise provided for, the previous version of the privacy policy will lapse and the updated version will come into force.9. Cross-Border Transfer of Personal InformationYour personal information will be transferred to and stored in servers and facilities located outside of the country where you live, which may have different personal data protection rules than in your country. When we transfer your personal information, we take steps to ensure that your information remains protected as required by applicable law, including through the use of binding written contracts.10. Cookies PolicyCookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.New Dinosaurs requires cookies in order to operate fully.We also work with third party vendors, including Google, use cookies to serve ads based on a user’s prior visits to our website or other websites.Further information about the cookies used by New Dinosaurs is provided below.The following cookie categories are based on the classification presented in the International Chambers of Commerce (ICC) Cookie Guide.Category 1: Strictly necessary cookiesThese cookies are essential to allow us to provide services that you have requested.Category 1 cookies used by New Dinosaurs:Login status – To identify you as being logged in to our website.Load balancing – Cookies may be used to distribute traffic across our web servers – to ensure that our websites perform well and give you the best possible experience.Shopping basket – Shopping basket cookies remember what is in your shopping basket.User subscription data – Subscription cookies allow us to ensure that you can access resources that you have registered for or paid for.Category 2: Performance cookiesThese cookies collect information about how visitors use our website, for instance, which pages visitors go to most often. The information collected by these cookies is aggregated, so these cookies don’t collect information that identifies individual visitors. The information collected is anonymous and is only used to improve the way our website works.Category 2 cookies used by New Dinosaurs:Web Analytics – Web analytics cookies are used to improve the design and user experience of our website by providing statistics on site usage and pages visited.Category 3: Functionality cookiesThese cookies allow us to remember choices you make (such as your user name, language or the region you are in) and provide enhanced, more relevant features.Category 3 cookies used by New Dinosaurs:User preferences – Preference cookies remember settings you’ve applied to this site such as layout, default views, search filters, a number of search results per page and, video bandwidth.Login information – Login cookies may be used to communicate your login details across pages of this website. These data are encrypted and not shared with third parties.User profile data – Email addresses, address and contact information. These are not shared with third parties.Category 4: Targeting or advertising cookiesThese cookies are used to deliver adverts that are more relevant to you and your interests. They are also used to limit the number of times you see an advert as well as help measure the effectiveness of the advertising campaign. They are usually placed by advertising networks with the website operator’s permission. They remember that you have visited a website and this information is shared with other organizations such as advertisers.Category 4 cookies used by New Dinosaurs:Targeted advertising – Advertising cookies are used by third parties to gather and send information to other websites so that they can present you with adverts that you might be interested in.New Dinosaurs uses the following third-party advertising networks:GoogleGoogle’s use of advertising cookies enables it and its partners to serve ads to you based on your visit to our sites and/or other sites on the Internet.You may opt out of personalized advertising by visiting Ads Settings.You may also want to check how Google manages data in its ads products here.Alternatively, you can opt out of a third-party vendor’s use of cookies for personalized advertising by visiting the following sites:aboutads.infoIn addition, third-party advertisers run adverts on New Dinosaurs and use their own advertising networks. If you would like to block cookies being set by third-party networks you may do so also through the preference settings on your browser.10. Contacting UsIf you have any questions, comments or requests regarding this privacy policy or our processing of your personal information, please contact us here. Popular DinosaursParasaurolophusBrontosaurusAlbertosaurusCompsognathusAllosaurusIguanodonSpinosaurusAnkylosaurusUtahraptorTyrannosaurus Popular Prehistoric AnimalsLiopleurodonPassenger PigeonDimorphodonAustralopithecusMegalodonHelicoprionElephant BirdArgentavisGlyptodonGigantopithecus About usContact usTerms of servicePrivacy policy © NewDinosaurs.com, 2019. All rights reserved.
This website uses cookies to ensure you get the best experience possible. You can read more about it here.     ACCEPT
